And then, yeah.
If you want to get started now, shall I wait a little bit longer?
Um, should we start now, G?
Yeah, I think so, because it's past quarter past now, so I think it's okay to
stop.
That would be one second. I'm just going to turn that computer off behind it.
Yeah, we're driving that. Okay, for it.
All of his text messages come through there, and it will be pinging the whole
time.
Okay, right. Hold on. Let me just see if I can remember how to do this, because
.
Okay, you see that? Yes. Perfect. Perfect. Ready to go? Yes, thank you so much.
Okay, no worries. So we were just saying I've done a really similar talk to
this before,
which I know was super helpful. So I basically dug the same PowerPoint out of
my archives
and just had a look over it. I have to be honest and say that even reading
through this now
has made me realise just how much things have changed and how much cameras help
me financially.
So I've updated this to kind of suit where I am now and then draw from my own
experience again.
I can honestly say that when we break down each of the reasons why we can, I've
now been all three people.
So I can really draw on that experience and hopefully share it and help it.
So we talk a lot in our community about feeling empowered as women.
Being online and being able to make money from your home in your own time
whilst you're sitting in bed, indulging your fantasies
and even while you get ready for a night out, it's truly a powerful feeling.
Along with independence, this inspires confidence in our appearance, gives us
the freedom to play around with our inner desires,
test our boundaries and often allows an escape from our own lives and problems
that we might be experiencing.
We also talk a lot about self-love and whilst we've all got different opinions
of what that looks like,
it usually involves a workout, a takeaway, a face mask or in my case, a large
glass of wine and waiting many Harry Potter films.
I'm lucky enough to have come full circle with canning that's really changed my
perspective, not just on money, but also my mindset and how I look after myself
.
I'm not shy in saying that I had my challenges in my life when I started and
after much help from lots of people that I met along the way
I now see various parts of myself as jigsaw pieces and the different parts of
me fit together nicely to make me a whole and happy human.
These pieces can be made up of various things, depending on who you are as a
person, but I usually find that when I'm neglecting one part of this puzzle,
say my mental health, I feel out of sorts and like the pieces just don't fit.
So what if I told you that your financial health is also one of your jigsaw
pieces and investing time in your finances is just as much self-love as a face
mask and a binge watch your twilight.
Ensuring that you're hitting your finance goals and making your money work for
you can be just as empowering as a night out with the girls or really glamorous
photo shoot.
Spending time on this piece of the jigsaw can also make your cam time much more
fulfilling and most importantly give you a better sense of control.
Oh, I just click it later. I was like, Oh God, I've got no pointers.
So this is a picture of my bum, which is not finance related, but I am very
clearly working in this photo and I'm also very proud of it.
So I'm happy to be able to share it again for the second time.
I just wanted to cover some topics that come up quite frequently alongside some
tips and tricks that you might find useful when getting you started on managing
your money.
So we're going to run through what self-employment means, what tax is all about
.
If you have a part time or a full time job alongside cam, some useful
information on targets and how to budget and make your cam money work for you.
Snowballing debt and most importantly, how money can affect your mindset and
how important it is to set yourself boundaries.
I think that the basics are always a really good place to start.
So I just wanted to confirm that whether cam is your full time job, part time
job or just a side hustle for some fun money, you are still self-employed.
This does mean that you'll need to register as being self-employed with HMRC
and to clear the money that you earn.
Not to do this is something called tax guidance and I'm not telling you this to
scare you, but just to make your ban.
Knowledge is always key and if you are aware, you can make the decision that
works best for yourself.
It's really, really easy to register as self-employed and I'm going to send out
some links after this.
Georgia will have to send them for me if that's okay.
Once the Zoom's finished, but just a simple Google will take you through HMRC's
webpage and it's super simple to be able to register.
If you're someone who's been hamming for a while and haven't yet registered as
self-employed, don't worry.
You just need to do this as soon as possible.
By registering, you're not incurring any cost, just declaring that you are self
-employed and that you are making money.
Being self-employed means that you do not pay tax monthly like you would if you
worked for say, Tesco.
You pay tax at the end of every year.
This can make it quite overwhelming and therefore it's always better to break
tax payable down into monthly, weekly and even daily segments that it does not
feel so huge.
We'll also look into this shortly.
The tax year runs from the 6th of April to the 5th of April every year.
You then have until the 31st of January the following year to submit your
return and pay any tax that you own.
This gives you plenty of time to save and to be aware of what you are earning.
This would mean that the tax year ended on the 5th of April 2023 and you would
not be expected to file your return or pay your tax up until the 31st of
January 2024.
So each person in the UK is allowed to earn £12,570 per year before they are
taxed.
We'll look at this next to ensure we will understand what this means for
different job types.
We aren't expected to be an expert in every field so while I think that it's
important we have an understanding of what tax means for us as individuals.
Investing in an accountant is just as important as investing in a good haird
resser.
What you're doing is not illegal and your accountant is likely to not be too
concerned.
If you're worried about approaching a stranger and having to explain, just
approach the agency.
They have accountants that they work with who are familiar with the job and are
less likely to ask questions that you might not feel comfortable answering.
I'm sure that most of you are aware that my job is a mortgage advisor and I've
done lots of mortgages for camgirls and girls who make money on OnlyFans.
If you don't declare your income HMR city, you can't use that towards a
mortgage which you might wish to get in the future.
You have to have it declared to the government before you're able to use it for
any kind of mortgage application.
I do understand that are we on our next one?
No.
Next slide.
I'll read in my own notes.
Question that I get asked a lot is what happens if you already have a job.
Working the day and coming in the evening is absolutely no different to having
a full-time job and perhaps selling in candles or things online in the evening
which we know is quite popular.
I put together some examples for a better understanding so hopefully this helps
.
I've done on here a full-time job versus part-time job so you can get an idea
of what kind of tax that you would be likely to pay.
If you have a full-time job and you're earning £16,000 per year, you've
already used up your personal allowance in that job.
You'll be paying taxes in your normal job monthly on your pay slip as you would
expect.
If you were then earning £500 per month on webcam, this would be £6,000 per
year which you would then need to pay tax on.
Tax is 20% of this so anyone pays tax at 20% over their personal allowance and
therefore your tax would be £1,200 for the year which is £100 a month so
breaking it down makes it a little bit easier to digest.
If you have a part-time job, things are slightly different.
If you earn, say, £8,000 per year, then you're only using part of your
personal allowance here so you've still got some of it left.
So you've got your £12,570 that you're able to earn tax free, minus your £8,
000 that you've earned which leaves you with £4,570 per year.
So we use the same amount again and you're earning £500 per month on webcam,
that would be £6,000 per year.
So you still have that £4,570 left of your personal allowance which means that
you're only paying tax on the difference between those two which would be £1,
430.
Again, your tax is 20% so it would be £286 for the year and £23, £83 per
month.
You can see there that it really does depend on what you're doing in your daily
life.
Obviously, if you don't have a full or a part-time job and cam is your only job
, then you're able to use that full personal allowance to the £12,570
completely for your cam income and you would only pay tax on anything over that
.
We're good.
Perfect.
So you're going to have to move this around the screen because it's covering up
some of the slides.
Okay, so in those examples, the tax might seem like a lot, but the tax payable
is no different than if you picked up like extra shifts.
If you had a pay rise or you've got a higher paid job or a second job, so it's
really no different than if you picked up extra shifts at your current job, you
'd be paying exactly the same tax.
You would just be paying it monthly instead of having to deal with it yourself.
So it's not more expensive.
It's exactly the same.
Obviously, you get a bit more freedom with camming anyway.
So offsetting is a way to pay less tax by taking the costs of running your
business from your profits.
So remember that what you're doing is essentially running a business and you
are able to take some of those expenses off of what you've earned so that your
tax liability is lower.
So I've listed from the government website what purchases you're allowed to
offset.
So this is directly from their website as to what they say you can offset as a
business owner.
So the things that you can offset are office costs, for example, stationary
phone bills, travel costs, for example, fuel parking, train or bus fares, any
clothing expenses.
So for example, any uniforms or anything that you might wear, staff costs, so
salaries or subcontractor costs, things that you buy to sell on.
So for example, stock or raw materials, financial costs, so insurance bank
charges that also applies to things like accountants, cost of any business
premises.
So heating, lighting, business rates, and then any advertising or marketing,
for example, any website costs.
So not all of these are going to apply to us because this is a really standard
list, but it's worth thinking about what you've spent on your camming and
keeping receipts.
And this is where an accountant is going to really help you and come into their
room with what you earn and what kind of expenses that you can claim.
So if you are feeling slightly nervous about what you can claim and what you
can't, then you can always ask an accountant and they'll be able to help you.
Okay, so I've done like a little example here of the kind of things that we can
use as expenses in the jobs that we do. So just to kind of give you some ideas
and to get you thinking.
So things like notebooks that you might use to keep notes on cam, any kind of
like webcams that you buy, ring lights, the clickers that we love so we can
take photos of ourselves.
Photo props, so if you've been asked to take a certain type of photo, and you
've got just a prop in order to be able to do that you're able to offset that as
well.
New laptops if you bought yourself a laptop, you can offset that cost, any
underwear that you might buy to sell on so I know a lot of girls kind of sell
underwear and things like that online.
So you can, if you're buying that specifically to sell it on technically
classes in the raw material. So you're able to then also have that as well.
And then any outfits that you wear on cam so if you have quite a specific thing
that you do on ham and you have an outfit you can also offset that cost as well
.
My example just here I've kind of used our 500 pounds per month camming and
paying 20% as tax just to stick to the same kind of figures and show you how
much of a difference it would make.
So I've kind of used an example here of the type of things that I would offset.
So a new webcam, a ring light and a clicker, my ring light breaks all the time
so I'm constantly finding that I have to buy new ones.
A sexy bomber jacket which I believe was a story that one of the girls used to
tell about having to wear a bomber jacket online for one of her clients.
So underwear to sell and then toys and underwear for cam so things that you're
buying for camming you can offset those as well.
Naturally that underwear is more expensive than what you're buying to sell on
to other people.
If you're chosen to use an accountant then you're able to offset that as well.
In that example there your total expenses would come to £520 so you would
actually deduct that off of the money that you've earned.
And as you can see there that means that your total income would be £5,480
instead.
And that means that your tax would then go down from £1,200 to £1,096.
So keep your receipts, go later about the benefits of having two bank accounts
to make expensive easier to work out and less time consuming for you.
I'm sure that you can agree it's definitely worth keeping an eye on this.
This kind of summarises how tax works but I do want to express again on how
important having an accountant is as it means that you won't have to worry
about yourself so it's completely worth the investment.
Is there any questions from anyone at this point?
I see some things in the chat.
Yeah of course we can send a PowerPoint that's fine I worry.
If we move on to the next one.
Okay I just wanted to run through some frequently asked questions that I've
seen on the group and just explain a little bit of background around these
questions so that hopefully you can put your mind at rest if you feel
uncomfortable about anything.
So again if you have any questions on these or if there's any questions I haven
't answered, I can chat box and then I can come back to you and answer those as
well at the end.
So always get questions about setting up a bank account and why they ask what
you do and how much it is that you earn.
So this is for two reasons, one being that all UK bank accounts are regulated
by something called the Financial Conduct Authority.
They need to ensure all banks need to ensure that your money is coming from a
legitimate source and it's not being laundered so you're not being given it by
somebody for any kind of criminal activity.
Your money is legitimate because it isn't criminal activity and if you're
registered and self-employed and you file any tax returns then you've got
absolutely nothing to worry about.
The second reason they asked this question and probably the most important is
that they like to basically see what they can bombard you with in terms of
marketing and how much you're going to be earning so that they can figure out
if they can sell your credit card.
You call this know your client and it's basically so that they can figure out
what type of person you are so they can do what we call targeted marketing.
So in terms of do I need to tell them what I do and things like that.
So your job title can be as creative as you want it to be.
Maybe a cam model is no different to any other profession and my friend who
works in a recruitment agency has given her staff the title of job finding nin
jas, which is really hard to find an insurance drop down.
Sure, you can kind of choose to be what you want, but some good examples are
just model, for example, or you can use content created, which is something
that I have used before in the past, because technically for all they know you
could be creating content on Instagram and that is no different really to
anything that we do.
So having two bank accounts is an absolutely essential, however, it can be a
really good way to manage your money. So, for example, I have a bank account
that my can money gets paid into, I keep my 20% tax in this account, and I use
this money for expenses that I might wish to offset.
It means that when I do my end of year accounts, everything is in one place
without having to sit through money I spend on KFC to find calm related
expenses, and then transfer any money left over into my normal spending account
for me to use as I wish.
It also means that my accountant doesn't see how much money I spend in KFC
either, which is better both of us.
So in relation to work, this is a question I get all the time. If you have a
full time job, you might find that your contract states that you're unable to
have another job.
This is what I like to call a fallback clause. It's something that they could
use should your behaviour and productivity be affected by another job.
If you were working all night in a bar and then you were too tired to perform
your daily job, they do have the right to be able to tell you to stop.
So just ensure that if you have a full time job, you're putting just as much
effort and time into that as you're coming.
Surviving on five hours sleep in the evening will not make your daytime fun,
trust me, I've definitely tried this and it definitely doesn't work.
So make sure if you do have a full time job, you're kind of prioritising that
as much as possible.
What if they find out is another question I get all the time. So remain
anonymous on cam is really important to some people, especially if you have a
full time job to minimise the risk of ever being recognised.
Don't talk about anything personal. Make up a fake job, a fake hometown and a
fake life. And remember, they're usually more embarrassed to admit that they
aren't at all work than you are, the one being paid.
So they're unlikely to ever really say anything.
So in terms of private payments, another thing that comes up quite often is
private payments.
I wanted to just reiterate that companies such as PayPal are also regulated by
the Financial Conduct Authority, which means they have to verify your identity
just the same as if you were to open an account with Monzo or Starling or
Barclays or any of those companies.
If you use a fake name with a PayPal account, it's technically classed as fraud
. And if you do get caught, they can keep your money and they can investigate
you.
There's absolutely nothing wrong with using PayPal if you're using your correct
name. However, if you want to remain anonymous, then I would keep all of your
earnings on AdultWork.
This also applies to any private payments through banking. So in the UK, we now
have to confirm the name with the person who owns the account that we are
paying money to.
So if they're paying money direct to your account and you give them a false
name, the bank is likely to alert them to this. They don't inform them of your
real name.
However, it can raise tricky questions with clients who think you genuinely are
your persona and I have also been there as well, so I can confirm it does raise
a few questions.
So if you don't want to be found, you want to keep completely anonymous, keep
all of your earnings on how it works because it limits any risk of anybody
finding out who you actually are.
Okay.
So I just wanted to talk a little bit about targets and budgeting and how to
shift your perspective on how you work.
So there's no right or wrong way to can and that we all know that it can
sometimes be quite inconsistent.
This is your business and you can work in exactly the way that you want and
that's the beauty of it.
These are some points and work installs that I personally found useful for me
over the four years now that I have been coming.
I've collected other people's tips as well as my own experiences together to
build what I think is an effective and proactive attitude to coming.
All of us can for completely different reasons. So I've tried to break these
down into three categories. However, you might be a mixture of you, which I've
definitely been at some point as well.
So firstly, we have coming for fun money, which is personally where I now find
myself.
There's three things that I think it's really important to bear in mind that
when you can for fun money, just like things like going out buying pair of
shoes or handbags or, you know, money for Friday night or something like that.
So consistency is super important throughout coming, regardless of why you're
doing it.
We all know how flat it can feel when you're going out this Saturday and you
log in on a Friday to get some money and it's absolutely dead.
And that's because nobody knows that you're online and they haven't come to
expect to see you on them.
Having days and times that you work, saying this example for Thursday and
Friday night means that you're more likely to pick up the same guys around the
same time and they'll come to expect you online.
This also secures your martini money and instead of earning it all in one night
and with on mammoth target you're doing it over two, possibly three days.
Working hours are super important and we all talk about when we're logging on,
but what time are you actually logging off so when do you know what time you
actually finished.
No, no, no, no, no, I'm back now sorry. That was a really nice face of mine I
was like.
So giving yourself four to five hours online and knowing that what it's done
you can do what you want.
Usually for me that means going to bed.
It's going to mean that you have a focus during those times and knowing when
you're finished usually improves your attitude to cam.
We have the same like home time and working hours in normal jobs so we should
definitely have them on cam as well.
It's really important to follow your mood and if you're doing well and want to
go absolutely go for it.
But if you're feeling tired log off at home time because you've done your hours
and you've committed you said you would.
George has done some really good goal sets and workshops before and I would
encourage everyone to watch these to understand the importance of breaking down
your goals as this really helps if you're just having four or say a handbag.
£500 is an absolutely huge target but £100 a week and you're likely to feel
the power of hitting the small goal boosting your mood and spurring you want to
hit the bigger one.
Okay with that we don't have any questions now.
Okay so coming to pay bills is how I spent most of my cam life.
Being able to pay my mortgage and my house bills has allowed my partner to
start a business that is very successful and definitely would not exist without
cam.
These are the three things that I personally always focus on when I'm coming
and doing my finance related self-love.
Working out how you actually need to make every day on cam will ensure that you
remain in control and not at all overwhelmed.
When we get paid daily it can feel impossible to get to say £500 per rent.
However if you break this down over each day you know how much you need to earn
and how much of this that you can actually then spend.
You'll feel much more secure allowing you to relax and enjoy your cam
experience as opposed to worrying which will come across in your attitude.
When you know how much you need to earn any money earned over this becomes what
I call your security buffer.
And I'll explain this how that works on the next slide.
So shift your mindset from home time to cam time is one of the most difficult
things that I have ever done.
However if you're working on the principle of having working hours during these
hours I prefer to be proactive.
The same as I would be as if I was in my office job when I'm online I leave
feedback reply to emails and set certain times to be in free.
This will feel more rank and troll of noise control and hopefully attract guys
to your room.
On the principle of being completely honest I did all show you to cam from my
bed on a Saturday morning and exceptionally drunk on a Sunday night.
I see this less of work and more of entertainment and that is just following my
mood which as we've said is also super important.
If you're feeling really overwhelmed with a large target and lots of bills to
pay you can be really easily led into doing things that you do not want to do
and thus creating really negative feelings towards your account and your money.
If you have someone come into your room ask the things that you do not do be
firm and positively communicate that this is not for you.
If they end the chat shift your perspective and instead of feeling negative for
it not being a long call.
They thanks for £2.30 and now I'm on to the next one they are literally paying
at that point just to ask you questions.
I cannot express how important that it is to remain in control of your
boundaries and not feel as though you have to do things in order to make money.
You'll start to resent town and it will definitely lose its fun and I have to
say I've also been there as well and kind of lost track of why I was doing it.
And just doing things that felt really uncomfortable just because I was
desperate to hit certain targets etc.
So set your reasonable target if you don't do it you don't do it and then you
just move on to the next one because the next one will come along.
Okay so I've done a little bill example here I don't think this has really
included the cost of living increase and this is definitely two years old but
we'll just use this one because I think I've kept the numbers quite simple here
so what I've done is I've just added together
what a normal person's bills would look like so you rent any council tax your
gas your food phone in Netflix and then a gym membership which I definitely don
't have but I know a lot of people do.
And I've totaled that up to what that would look like for a monthly basis.
So instead of thinking I need to earn £930 as quickly as I possibly can you
break that down so working five days a week because it's really important to
give our self time off.
That works out to be £46.50 per day as 83 credits and that's at two credits
per minute.
That's actually only 41 and a half minutes of connected call time per day so if
you're setting yourself a certain amount of hours to work you know that
actually you only have to have a connected call time of that long to be able to
hit what you want to go for.
Anything that you earn over that is then your buffer so for example one day you
earn £120 but the next you only earn £30 you're actually still on track and
consistency is key so you're adding that money into your budget rather than
thinking
oh great I can go out and now spend that.
Okay.
Did not take into consideration that this little box would be right over
everything I need to read.
Okay so this one I think is the most important one for me and I know that a lot
of people also feel the same way so definitely not ashamed to say that the
reason that I started coming was to reduce my own debts and give myself a
better lifestyle because it was
very overwhelming and I can happily and very proudly say that using this method
I've paid off over £22,000 of debt in four years.
I did that in the beginning part of my cam journey I now don't need to do that
anymore so I can't have achieved that goal and then moved on to being able to
build money and things like that so a lot of the points on here are the same as
coming to pay bills but as reducing your debt isn't actually something that's
completely essential.
It's not necessarily what you need to earn but more what you want to earn.
There's a question that's just popped up.
Oh thank you.
Yeah so it's not what you need to earn it's more what you want to earn so it's
you leading your own targets which also can be quite daunting as well.
So I'm going to explain something called snowballing shortly which is how I
managed to do what I did however it's really important to set up small but
regular and achievable goals.
Thinking that you need to earn £300 to pay a credit card is a huge target and
can leave you feeling like it's an absolute mountain to climb.
Earning £40 a week is a much easier target to digest and as you'll see it can
make a massive difference.
Your mindset and rewarding yourself are really important because sitting and
staring at a screen for hours to pay off debt can really create a lot of
negativity and it will make you feel like you're not gaining anything.
You don't get to spend this money yourself you're paying the things you've
already bought so you feel no enjoyment from getting that money at all
especially if it's been quite a difficult evening.
If you're working for £40 to pay off your credit card you've got two options
you either log off when you've done and say I've done my bit now I'm finished I
'm now going to go and enjoy myself.
Or if you earn extra money over and above that target use it for yourself and
as a reward for make £40 for the credit card £10 for your bottle of wine you
're absolutely winning that's your that's your treat for doing what you've done.
Again boundaries are really important and I suffered with this myself.
I was really desperate to pay off my debt and I would literally do anything
tolerate anyone and consequently I completely forgot my own self were.
If you do one thing take control you are in the decision to reduce your debt
and ensure lifestyle that you are happy with.
This doesn't mean that you need to do things that make you feel negative and it
doesn't mean that you need to do things that you don't want to do because of
that.
This one next is an example of what we call snowballing so if you imagine you
're not clapping a snowball together like that you're putting on the floor and
you're rolling it up like you would do with a snowman.
It involves starting with your smallest debt over paying to clear it and then
rolling that monthly payment into your next debt.
So breaking this down into smaller goals is a much better way of clearing and
reducing debt and allowing us to feel less overwhelmed.
So in this example here I've got three kind of credit cards here so a credit
card, a PayPal credit account and then it's a card.
So the monthly repayments on those I've put next to it that's just an example
but if you've decided to try and reduce this you need to start small because
small goals are easier to achieve and will make you feel much better about
hitting that goal.
So if you set your target you're going to do £50 a week and you're going to
make that as an extra payment.
You pick your smallest debt so in this situation it would be the next card.
Continue to make all of your normal minimum payments on the other debts but
focus mostly on your smallest one.
So you earn your hundred credits per week.
Remember that the rest is your fund money so you get to spend that yourself.
You pay your £50 a week off to your next card.
That means that you would have actually have paid that off in three weeks I've
put four there because I clearly can't do mental maths but you would have paid
it off in three weeks.
That will spur you on so you'll think perfect that's done it's paid off amazing
I'm so proud of myself.
Now I'm going to take that and move it on to the next one.
So that monthly payment that you can do on your next card of £20 a month you
then add that into your £50 a week target.
So it wasn't yours you weren't used to having it anywhere you need to take that
payment and add it into what you're paying off.
This means that adding into your weekly payment of £50 you now pay £55.
So you move that on to smallest debt like before and that would be your PayPal
credit account.
So you'll start paying off £55 a week of your PayPal credit account.
Another four weeks and then that will be gone and you'll think amazing I've got
rid of two of my debts and now I move on to the next one and you do exactly the
same as you did before.
You take your monthly repayment you were paying previously add it into your
budget and then you move on with that one and hopefully you'll get to the point
where you're feeling really really good you've really achieved something and
then you can clear off the last one
and hopefully carry on coming for fun money and you move over into the other
category where you can buy these and have bags without having to use your
credit card.
Hopefully all of that makes sense.
Okay now this is where I can get a bit rambly so I am sorry but I just wanted
to kind of summarize everything I've gone through there so hopefully I haven't
already bought you to death but I promised I'll be finished very shortly.
So it's no secret to anyone who knows me that I am a massive control free and I
have spreadsheets and notebooks that would absolutely blow people's minds.
I now have to label my own notebook so I know which one is which and what I'm
actually writing said notebook.
It makes me feel comfortable as a person I like to be in control of things like
that.
I very much viewed webcam as a business so for me putting in 100% effort
between 45 hours a day and then logging off when I was finished really helped
me to maintain my mindset on cam and not get caught up.
I personally work out what I've earned after every single call even if it's
only a couple of minutes.
It isn't for everybody and I know I'm a bit of control freak but it does make
you feel a little bit more positive so I'd encourage you to write at least
something down whilst you're online so even if it's out there you can write
down what you've earned.
It can be quite difficult to take it from credits through to what that means
for you in monetary terms, especially if you've had a night with you kind of
having four minute calls five minute calls can add up really quickly and when
you're writing it down and you're thinking that's actual money.
It can sometimes feel a little bit better if you're having a bit of a slow one.
That negative feeling that you get when you're chatting to a guy and he just
logged out I hate that feeling it really really bugs me for such a long time.
I shifted my mindset from oh that's you obviously like me or whatever he's
decided to that's just you know that's just a shame.
It's not the end of the world. I'd immediately write down how much that made me
and then I take the positive so great that was £5.20 now I'm on to the next
one.
Guys that brow through free and log in and out is no different to you lot
browsing like she in or Amazon in my case.
Sometimes they're just being a little bit nosy and other times they're kind of
seeing what they're likely to get.
Remember these guys work for this money as well and some of them have a
specific desire or that they need a need that they're looking for that they
want to see if you can film.
It's a bit like checking the reviews when you go to buy something to see if it
's largely to fit you when they're asking questions try to remember that that's
what they're doing.
Be honest and open about what you will and what you won't do because it will
put less pressure on you and if they do take you private and then they log out
well then you just weren't going to fit them the same as that outfit wasn't
going to fit you.
Free that free can be really, really overwhelming and it definitely was for me
when I started and it can be really annoying being bombarded with questions but
probably just as annoying as if you owned an Etsy shop and you were trying to
sell something
and people keep asking you questions over and over again about it.
Just remember that you wouldn't be expected in that situation to answer
questions for hours and hours on end so make sure that you just set yourself
timer so that you're not in free constantly.
And if you're not enjoying it, you do your 20 minutes and then you come back
out of free because you're not expected to just constantly be asking questions.
Changing your perspective on those really small things can make really big
difference in your attitude and I can promise you that this will definitely be
visible on cam.
Just wanted to say that our diversity is one of the best places to ask for help
if you're struggling or do not understand anything.
I've now been coming for four years and I've yet to find a girl who minds a
direct message or someone who doesn't get a reply on any of the group chats.
It's really, really important that we bear in mind that managing our money well
and just generally being like absolute badass business, business women is
really, really powerful feeling and it will absolutely radiate from you not
just on cam but also in the rest of your life as well because
you feel more positive, you'll feel happier and you'll feel like all of your
jokes or puzzle pieces just fit yourself together.
And that is me done that okay.
That was absolutely amazing that was so good.
Yeah, if I send you through that PowerPoint, do you want to send that to, I
know, one of the girls asked for it there.
And then you can just send it over and all the calculations for everything on
there is that okay.
Absolutely, if it's okay with you we can put it on the website as well in the
members area.
I know that some people messaged me saying they can make it but they want to
watch that so yeah absolutely fine.
I also do have just in case it is of any interest to anybody.
I have an Excel spreadsheet that I've designed myself that works out if you
type in how much credits you've earned it will work out what your monetary
figure of that is.
And also one that works out where you have what you weren't the day before to
what you weren't today what the difference between those two is so you can work
out what your figure of earnings is really easily.
So I don't know if everyone uses Excel but if anybody would like that then you
know.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a very controlled spreadsheet kind of thing.
Sorry, George, I didn't get you there.
Thank you, that was so so good so amazing so informative and yeah I loved all
the things you said about your journey on cam and stuff like that made me feel
super proud of you.
Thank you. I can't believe it's been four years when I was typing that it said
two and then I thought that was actually nearly two years ago so it has been
four years.
Thank you very much ladies. Thank you so much Kelly honestly that was amazing I
mean I was expecting it to be informative but it was like inspirational as well
so thank you for your individual advice and everything so it was amazing.
No worries, I'll leave you ladies to it. Thank you very much. See you Kelly.
Bye. Bye.